Guide to the Kevin Killian and Dodie Bellamy Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1973-2015; Series I; 23.25; 25 boxes
  - Alphabetical correspondence
    - Glancy, Diane, 1987, undated (Box 8)
    - Glazier, Loss Pequeno, 1997, undated (Box 8)
    - Gloeckner, Phoebe, 1999-2003, undated (Box 8)
    - Gluck, Bob, 1984-1996, undated; 2 (Box 8)
    - Golding, Alan, 1983, undated (Box 8)
    - Goldsmith, Kenneth, 1995 (Box 8)
    - Goldstein, Mark, 2007 (Box 8)
    - Goldstein, Robert, 1984-1985, undated (Box 8)
    - Gomez, Jewelle, 1984 (Box 8)
    - Gooch, Brad, 1992, undated (Box 8)
    - Goodman, Craig, undated (Box 8)
    - Gordon, Sam, 2007, undated (Box 8)
    - Grady, Paul, 1984-1996, undated (Box 8)
    - Grahn, Judy, 1984-2013, undated (Box 8)
    - Graham, Don, 1990 January 23 (Box 8)
    - Graham, Lorraine, 2005 May 16 (Box 8)
    - Granger, John, 1985-1987, undated (Box 8)
    - Gray, Janet, undated (Box 8)
    - Gray, Tim, undated (Box 8)
    - Greene, Matthew, 2003-2004, undated; 2 (Box 8)
    - Greenfield, Sonia, undated (Box 8)
    - Greyson, John, 1989-1990, undated (Box 8)
    - Gricewith, Andy, 2005 (Box 8)
    - Grider, Nicholas, undated (Box 8)
    - Grim, Jessica, 1985-1997, undated; 2 (Box 8)
    - Gudath, Lauren, undated (Box 8)
    - Guest, Barbara, 1996-2003, undated; 2 (Box 8)
    - Guest, Graham, 2008, undated (Box 8)
    - Guichard, Philip, 1999, undated (Box 8)
    - Gunn, Thom, 1994–1995 (Box 8)
    - Gurba, Myriam, 2013, undated (Box 8)
    - Guterson, David, 1997 June 18 (Box 8)
    - Gutherie, Camille, 1996, undated (Box 8)
    - Gwinette, David, 1997, undated (Box 8)
    - Haber, Zack, 2014, undated (Box 8)
    - Hacker, Marilyn, 1985-1993, undated (Box 8)
    - Hagedorn, Jessica, 1987, undated (Box 8)
    - Hale, Robert, 1994, undated (Box 8)
    - Hale-Jones, Tanesia, 2006, undated (Box 8)
    - Haley, Albert, 1983 April 18 (Box 8)
    - Hall, Richard, 1985 (Box 8)
    - Halpern, Rob, 1997-2003, undated (Box 8)
    - Halsey, Alan, 1985 (Box 8)
    - Hamilton, Roxi, 2003, undated (Box 8)
    - Hammer, Jonathan, 1991-1995, undated (Box 8)
    - Hankwitz, Molly, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Hanley, Jack, 1995-2005, undated (Box 8)
    - Hanna, Julia, 1990, undated (Box 8)
    - Hannibal, Shauna, 1996, undated (Box 8)
    - Harden, Heather, 2003 (Box 8)
    - Hardy, Hollie, 2006 November 10 (Box 8)
    - Harrington, Douglas, 1981 December 01 (Box 9)
    - Harris, Kaplan Page, undated (Box 9)
    - Harrison, Bob, 1995, undated (Box 9)
    - Harryman, Carla, 1993-1996, undated (Box 9)
    - Carla Harryman/Barrett Watten, 2003 December 02 (Box 9)
    - Harryman, Carla (IOU Theater 1995 Poets Theater at Intersection), 1993–1995 (Box 9)
    - Hass, Robert, 2001 April 26 (Box 9)
    - Haug, Matt, 1990 May 31 (Box 9)
    - Haule, Robert, 1986-1987, undated (Box 9)
    - Hawkins, Lamar, 2003 May 16 (Box 9)
    - Hawkins, Richard, 1991, undated (Box 9)
    - Hayes, Joe, undated (Box 9)
    - Heames, Ian, undated (Box 9)
    - Heffron, Debby, 1972 (Box 9)
    - Heim, Scott, 1995-1997, undated (Box 9)
    - Heinowitz, R. Cole, 1995 (Box 9)
    - Hejinian, Lyn, 1994-2003, undated (Box 9)
    - Helfand, Glen, undated (Box 9)
    - Hell, Richard, 1989, undated (Box 9)
    - Heller, Michael, 1987 (Box 9)
    - Hengst, Clifford, undated (Box 9)
    - Henning, Barbara, 2004, undated (Box 9)
    - Henriksen, Tom, 1985, undated (Box 9)
    - Henson, Beth, 2004 (Box 9)
    - Herd, Colin, undated (Box 9)
    - Herndon, Fran, 1994 May 30 (Box 9)
    - Herzig, Carl, 1984–1985 (Box 9)
    - Heuving, Jeanne, 2003 (Box 9)
    - Hewicker, Scott, 1985, undated (Box 9)
    - Heyer, Colleen, undated (Box 9)
    - Heyer, Maryanne, 1978, undated (Box 9)
    - Hickman, Leland, 1986-1990, undated (Box 9)
    - Higgs, Matthew, 2003 November 24 (Box 9)
    - High, John, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Highfill, Mitch, 1996 (Box 9)
    - Hill, Crag, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Hill, Lindsay, 2006 August 26 (Box 9)
    - Hillman, Brenda, 1999-2006, undated (Box 9)
    - Hoctel, Patrick, 1989, undated (Box 9)
    - Hofer, Jen, 1994–1996 (Box 9)
    - Hoff, Doris, 1986–1989 (Box 9)
    - Hoff, Jennifer, 1991–1994 (Box 9)
    - Holden, Kristen, 2005, undated (Box 9)
    - Hollander, Benjamin, 1987-1988, undated (Box 9)
    - Hollo, Anselm, 1997 (Box 9)
    - Hollo, Jane Dalrymple, undated (Box 9)
    - Holloway, Evan, undated (Box 9)
    - Holloway, Rob, undated (Box 9)
    - Hollowell, Andrea, 1987, undated (Box 9)
    - Holt, Hazel, 1988 August 30 (Box 9)
    - Holt, Kelly, undated (Box 9)
    - Holtz, William, 1994 August 19 (Box 9)
    - Hoover, Paul, 1996, undated (Box 9)
    - Horvitz, Philip, 1997, undated (Box 9)
    - House, Tom, 1999–2006 (Box 9)
    - Howe, Fanny, 1985-1998, undated (Box 9)
    - Howe, Susan, 1988–2005 (Box 9)
    - Howe, William R., 2004 (Box 9)
    - Hsu, Bill, 1995 (Box 9)
    - Hubin, Allen J., 1967 June 16 (Box 9)
    - Huff, Michelle, 1981 May 05 (Box 9)
    - Hume, Christine, undated (Box 9)
    - Hunt, Erica, undated (Box 9)
    - Hunt, Laird, 1996, undated (Box 9)
    - Huston, Bo, undated (Box 9)
    - Iijima, Brenda, 1998-2001, undated (Box 9)
    - Inman, Peter, 1992, undated (Box 9)
    - Irby, Ken, 1987 April 08 (Box 9)
    - Clifford Irving Show, undated (Box 9)
      1 CD-R removed for separate housing. See Box 86.
    - Iyall, Debora, undated (Box 9)
    - Jackson, Earl Jr., 1989-1995, undated; 2 (Box 10)
    - Jackson, Jo, undated (Box 10)
    - Jacobson, Colter, undated (Box 10)
    - Jaffer, Francis, 1985-1987, undated (Box 10)
    - Jalet, Kim, 1989, undated (Box 10)
    - James, Gina, 2004 August 04 (Box 10)
    - Jane, Xaylor, 2004, undated (Box 10)
    - Januzzi, Marissa, 1995-1996, undated (Box 10)
    - Jarnagin, Willa, undated (Box 10)
    - Jamot, Lisa, 1994-2006, undated (Box 10)
    - Jenkins, Edith, undated (Box 10)
    - Jeppesen, Travis, undated (Box 10)
    - Jessup, Brad, 2014, undated (Box 10)
    - Jimenez, Jason, undated (Box 10)
    - Johnson, Colleen, 1978 July 30 (Box 10)
    - Johnson, Honor, 1987, undated (Box 10)
    - Johnson, Ray, undated (Box 10)
    - Johnson, Ray and Sharla Sava, undated (Box 10)
    - Johnston, Devin, undated (Box 10)
    - Jones, GB, 1991–2003; 3 (Box 10)
    - Jones, William E, 2007, undated (Box 10)
    - Joron, Andrew, 1994-1999, undated (Box 10)
    - Joselow, Beth, 1991, undated (Box 10)
    - Joyce, Brian, undated (Box 10)
    - Junker, Howard, 1984-1998, undated (Box 10)
    - Kane, Sarah, undated (Box 10)
    - Karol, Pamela (La Loca), 1987 (Box 10)
    - Karr, John, 1984-1985, undated (Box 10)
    - Kasak, Fred, 1996 July 23 (Box 10)
    - Katko, Justin, 2009 July 16 (Box 10)
    - Kaye, Richard, 1987 (Box 10)
    - Kearney, Lawrence, 1988, undated (Box 10)
    - Keilin, Corry, 1996 April 25 (Box 10)
    - Kelley, Mike, undated (Box 10)
    - Kemp, Arnold, 1994-2008, undated (Box 10)
    - Kemp, Carolyn, 1984-1991, undated (Box 10)
    - Kendall, Carol, 1995 (Box 10)
    - Kenney, Maurice, 1985, undated (Box 10)
    - Killian Family, 1983-1989, undated; 3 (Box 10)
    - Killian, Anne, undated (Box 10)
    - Catherine Killian Estate, 2008 (Box 10)
    - Killian, David, 1979-1988, undated (Box 10)
    - Killian, Kevin, 1995-2013, undated; 2 (Box 10)
    - Killian, Maureen, 1978-1998, undated; 2 (Box 10)
    - Killian, Nancy, 1989-1990, undated; 2 (Box 10)
    - Killian, Summer, 1996–2007 (Box 11)
    - Killian, Tim and Anne, 1977-1987, undated (Box 11)
    - Kim, Geraldine, 2005 October (Box 11)
    - Kim, Myung Mi, 1996–1999 (Box 11)
    - Kingsolver, Barbara, 1998 August 13 (Box 11)
    - Kinloch, David, 1995-1996, undated (Box 11)
    - Kinney Brothers, 1993–1995 (Box 11)
    - Kinsella, John, 1996, undated (Box 11)
    - Klawitter, George, 1984 (Box 11)
    - Klein, Darin, 2007, undated (Box 11)
    - Klobucar, Andrew, 2001, undated (Box 11)
    - Knuth, Kate, 1990-1992, undated (Box 11)
    - Kocik, Robert, undated (Box 11)
    - Kolokithas, Dawn, 1985-1986, undated (Box 11)
    - Koskovich, Gerard, undated (Box 11)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, 1995 (Box 11)
    - Kotz, Liz, 1991-1994, undated; 3 (Box 11)
    - Krafft, Tim, undated (Box 11)
    - Kramer, Wendy, 1995, undated; 2 (Box 11)
    - Kraus, Chris, 2000, undated (Box 11)
    - Krech, Richard, 2007, undated (Box 11)
    - Krell, Noah, undated (Box 11)
    - Kreml, Sandi, 1987-1989, undated; 2 (Box 11)
    - Kuehmeier, Karen A, 1997, undated (Box 11)
    - Kuszai, Joel, 1995-1996, undated (Box 11)
    - Kyger, Joanne, 1989 (Box 11)
    - LaBruce, Bruce, 2002, undated (Box 11)
    - Labonte, Richard, 1997, undated (Box 11)
    - Lafreniere, Steve, 1990-1994, undated (Box 11)
    - Lamantia, Philip, 2005, undated (Box 11)
    - Lambda Rising Book Report, 1989, undated (Box 11)
    - Lance, Jeanne, 1987-1989, undated (Box 11)
    - Landers, Susan, 2003, undated (Box 11)
    - Landress, Emily, 2013 (Box 11)
    - Larsen, David, 2003 December 02 (Box 11)
    - Gibbons, John Langan, 1992 November 17 (Box 11)
    - Lansing, Gerrit, 1995-2002, undated; 2 (Box 11)
    - Laporte, Mat, undated (Box 11)
    - Larsen, David, 1995-2003, undated (Box 11)
    - Larventz, Don, 1985-1988, undated (Box 11)
    - Lassell, Michael, 1992, undated (Box 11)
    - Latimer, Tirza, undated (Box 11)
    - Latzky, Eric, 1991, undated (Box 11)
    - Lauer, Kristin, 1978-1989, undated; 2 (Box 11)
    - Laughtland, Amanda, 2007 February 20 (Box 11)
    - Lauterbach, Ann, 1991–1995 (Box 11)
    - Lawlor, Andrea, undated (Box 11)
    - Lawrence, Nick, 1995-1996, undated (Box 11)
    - Lawson, Don S, 1991-1992, undated (Box 11)
    - Lease, Joseph, 1995, undated; 2 (Box 11)
    - Leddy, Michael, 1995-1996, undated (Box 11)
    - Lederer, Katherine, 1995, undated (Box 11)
    - LeDoux, Neil, undated; 2 (Box 11)
    - Lee, Matty, 2006, undated (Box 11)
    - Lehman, David, 1988, undated (Box 11)
    - Lehmann, Minnette, 2005 September 22 (Box 11)
    - Leonard, Cathy, 1981, undated (Box 11)
    - Lerner, Ben, 2006 (Box 11)
    - Leventhal, Stan, 1984-1989, undated (Box 11)
    - Lever, Nathen, 1997-1998, undated (Box 11)
    - Levi Strauss, David, 1986-1989, undated (Box 11)
    - Levin, Ira, 1997 December 18 (Box 11)
    - Levin, Shaun, undated (Box 11)
    - Levin, Sheree, undated (Box 11)
    - Levine, Stacey, 1993, undated (Box 11)
    - Leviton, Richard, undated (Box 11)
    - Levitsky, Rachel, undated (Box 11)
    - Levy, Andrew, 1990-1995, undated (Box 12)
    - Levy, Herb, undated (Box 12)
    - Lewis, Sinclair, 1941 February 25 (Box 12)
    - Leyland, Winston, 1982 March 19 (Box 12)
    - Liddy, James, undated (Box 12)
    - Lightman, Ira, 1994-1996, undated (Box 12)
    - Lilly, Jeffrey, 2004, undated (Box 12)
    - Lindquist, Catherine, 1986-1991, undated; 2 (Box 12)
    - Lindquist, Ed, 1982-2006, undated; 2 (Box 12)
    - Linwood, Elliott, undated (Box 12)
    - Lisicky, Paul, 2003 May 27 (Box 12)
    - Liu, Timothy, 1999 (Box 12)
    - Loden, Rachel, undated (Box 12)
    - Lonehood, Lex, 1994 November 28 (Box 12)
    - Long, Paul, 1997 (Box 12)
    - Longaway, Jane, 1986-1987, undated (Box 12)
    - Lookingbill, Colleen, 1996 (Box 12)
    - Loomis, Gloria, 1994 (Box 12)
    - Lopez, Tony, 1998-1999, undated (Box 12)
    - Lore, Matthew, 1995 (Box 12)
    - Lowander, Alison, 1984 May 13 (Box 12)
    - Lowenthal, Michael, 1996, undated (Box 12)
    - Lowther, John, 1997, undated (Box 12)
    - Lu, Pamela, 2000, undated (Box 12)
    - Lubeski, Lori, 1989-1995, undated; 2 (Box 12)
    - Lucas, Brian, 1995-1996, undated (Box 12)
    - Ludwar, Terry, 1985-1991, undated (Box 12)
    - Luoma, Bill, 1995-1997, undated (Box 12)
    - Lutz, Dietmar, undated (Box 12)
    - Lynn, Jason, undated (Box 12)
    - Lynn, Kathy, 1982 August 03 (Box 12)
    - Lyons, Kimberly, 2003-2005, undated (Box 12)
    - Lyon, Melinda, 1984 May 23 (Box 12)
    - Lyss, Heidi, 2004 July 26 (Box 12)
    - Macaulay, Charles, 1991, undated (Box 12)
    - Maccormack, Karen / Steve Mccaffrey, 1991, undated (Box 12)
    - McGee, Michael, undated (Box 12)
    - McGuire, Anne, 2011 July 02 (Box 12)
    - Macher, Sabine, 1986, undated (Box 12)
    - Macintyre, Mary, 1995-1996, undated (Box 12)
    - MacKieman, Elizabeth, 1995, undated (Box 12)
    - Macleod, Kathryn, 1991 (Box 12)
    - Macleod, Scott, 1998-2006, undated (Box 12)
    - Mac Low, Jackson, 1995-1996, undated (Box 12)
    - Maddin, Guy, undated (Box 12)
    - Magee, Kevin, 1995-2000, undated; 2 (Box 12)
    - Magee, Michael, undated (Box 12)
    - Mahoney, Mickey Ray, undated (Box 12)
    - Main, Thomas, 2001-2002, undated (Box 12)
    - Malasauskas, Raimundas, 2005 (Box 12)
    - Malcolm, Bruce, 1983-1991, undated (Box 12)
    - Mallamo, Lance, 1995-1996, undated (Box 12)
    - Malnichuck, John, undated (Box 12)
    - Malone, eric, 1993-1998, undated; 2 (Box 12)
    - Mandel, Tom, undated (Box 13)
    - Mangin, Daniel, 1991, undated (Box 13)
    - Mangold, Sarah, 2006 (Box 13)
    - Mania, Andrew, 2004-2005, undated (Box 13)
    - Manson, Peter, 1994, undated (Box 13)
    - Marek, Valerie, 1992, undated (Box 13)
    - Mariah, Paul, 1984-1985, undated (Box 13)
    - Mark, Don Chan, 1990, undated (Box 13)
    - Marks, Jim, 1996, undated (Box 13)
    - Marlatt, Daphne, undated (Box 13)
    - Marlow, Shelly, 1992 (Box 13)
    - Marschalk, Eric Phelps, 1995 (Box 13)
    - Marxer, Emma, 1998 (Box 13)
    - Mascaro, John, 1986-1988, undated (Box 13)
    - Massey, Joseph, undated (Box 13)
    - Martin, Chris and Dodie, undated (Box 13)
    - Martin, Douglas A., 2006 July 22 (Box 13)
    - Martin, John, 1995, undated (Box 13)
    - Martin, Pam, undated (Box 13)
    - Martin, Tim, 1987 June 05 (Box 13)
    - Mattilda, 2004 (Box 13)
    - Mascaro, John/ Gail Smith, 1985-1987, undated (Box 13)
    - Maud, Ralph, 1995-2005, undated (Box 13)
    - Mayer, Bernadette, 1989, undated (Box 13)
    - Mayerson, Keith, 1994, undated (Box 13)
    - Mayes, Frances, 1987 April 27 (Box 13)
    - McAlpin, Loring, 1990-2001, undated (Box 13)
    - McCann, Richard, 1989-1991, undated (Box 13)
    - McCarthy, Paul, 1993, undated (Box 13)
    - McClure, Amy Evans, undated (Box 13)
    - McClure, Michael, 2004 December 15 (Box 13)
    - McCormack, Derek, 2004, undated (Box 13)
    - McCourt, James, 1988-1994, undated (Box 13)
    - McCreary, Chris, undated (Box 13)
    - McElligott, Michael, undated (Box 13)
    - McGehee, Peter, 1987, undated (Box 13)
    - McGinnes, Mac, 2002 December 24 (Box 13)
    - McGregor, Janet, 1990–1991 (Box 13)
    - McGregor, Mary, 1997 March 12 (Box 13)
    - McGuire, Anne, 2005–2013 (Box 13)
    - McKeown, Adam, 1993, undated (Box 13)
    - McKinney, Casey, 2008 (Box 13)
    - McKinnon, Barry, 1987-1992, undated (Box 13)
    - McLeod, Kathryn, 1993, undated (Box 13)
    - McNally, John, undated (Box 13)
    - McNaughton, Duncan, 1995–2007 (Box 13)
    - McNaughton, Duncan and Michael Carr, 2007, undated (Box 13)
    - Meadows, Deborah, 2004 (Box 13)
    - Medrich, Alice, 1983-1984, undated (Box 13)
    - Meetze, James, undated (Box 13)
    - Mellis, Miranda, 2014 April 15 (Box 13)
    - Melnick, David, 1985 (Box 13)
    - Meltzre, David, undated (Box 13)
    - Mendoza, Jackie, 1990–1993 (Box 13)
    - Menefee, Sarah, 1996, undated (Box 13)
    - Meredith, Paul, undated (Box 13)
    - Meredith, Ruth, undated (Box 13)
    - Mewshaw, Michael, 1989 (Box 13)
    - Meyers, Richard (Cuz), 1989 (Box 13)
    - Micheline, Jack, 1986 (Box 13)
    - Millennium-Coming, 1995 (Box 13)
    - Miller, Bett, 1991–1992 (Box 13)
    - Miller, Laura, 1992 (Box 13)
    - Miller, Rebecca, undated (Box 13)
    - Miller, Tim, 1991–1997 (Box 13)
    - Milosevich, Karla, 2004, undated (Box 13)
    - Mirra, Helen, 1998, undated (Box 13)
    - Mischkot, Jono, undated (Box 13)
    - Mitchell-Dayton, Alfred, 1991 November 04 (Box 13)
    - Mitchell-Dayton, Caitlin, 1997-2006, undated (Box 13)
    - Mitchell-Dayton, Peter, 1995 (Box 13)
    - Mittenhal, Robert, 1995 (Box 13)
    - Miyamoto, Domi, undated (Box 13)
    - Mlinko, Ange, 1994-1995, undated (Box 13)
    - Moloney, Nancy, 1988-1989, undated (Box 13)
    - Moncrieff, Karen, 1992, undated (Box 13)
    - Montalbano, Karen, 2014 February 13 (Box 13)
    - Monte, Bryan, 1984-1985, undated (Box 13)
    - Moore, Candace, 2004 December 24 (Box 13)
    - Moore, Bill, 1985–2005 (Box 13)
    - Moore, Patrick, 1990-1991, undated (Box 13)
    - Moore, Richard 0., 1993 May 11 (Box 13)
    - Moore, Thurston, 2005 (Box 13)
    - Morariu, Janis, undated (Box 13)
    - Moriarty, Laura, 1985-1997, undated (Box 13)
    - Morris, Ed Jr., 1995-1996, undated (Box 13)
    - Morris, Jason, undated (Box 13)
    - Morrison, Yedda, 1997 February 13 (Box 13)
    - Morrow, Bradford, 1986, undated (Box 13)
    - Morse, Jesse, 2007-2008, undated (Box 13)
    - Mosher, Donal, undated (Box 13)
    - Moss, Leland, 1990 (Box 13)
    - Mossin, Andrew, 1994-1995, undated (Box 14)
    - Mot, Jan, undated (Box 14)
    - Moure, Erin, undated (Box 14)
    - Mossin, Andrew, 1993, undated (Box 14)
    - Moxley, Jennifer, 1994-2012, undated; 7 (Box 14)
    - Moyer, Carrie, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Mulford, Wendy, 1989 September 24 (Box 14)
    - Mullen, Harryette, 1987, undated (Box 14)
    - Mullen, Laura, 2003 December 08 (Box 14)
    - Murdoc, Johnny "Swat", undated (Box 14)
    - Murphy, Jay, 1995-2003, undated; 2 (Box 14)
    - Murphy, Sheila E., 1990-1995, undated (Box 14)
    - Murray, Beth, 1997-2004, undated (Box 14)
    - Mycue, Edward, 1984–1985 (Box 14)
    - Myers, John L., undated (Box 14)
    - Myles, Eileen, 1986-1993, undated; 2 (Box 14)
    - Nakell, Martin, 2003–2004 (Box 14)
    - Nava, Michael, undated (Box 14)
    - Naylor, Paul, 1995, undated (Box 14)
    - Neilson, Melanie, 1990–1996 (Box 14)
    - Neumeyer, Peter, 1999–2004 (Box 14)
    - Newlin, Paul, 1983 March 25 (Box 14)
    - Newmar, Julie, 1999 May 06 (Box 14)
    - Newton, Ryan, 2005-2006, undated (Box 14)
    - Ngai, Sianne, 1993-1997, undated (Box 14)
    - Nguyen, Hoa, 1997, undated (Box 14)
    - Nguyen, Hoa and Dale Smith, undated (Box 14)
    - Nicoloff, Michael, 2007, undated (Box 14)
    - Nichols, Miriam, 1995-2001, undated (Box 14)
    - Nickoladze, Nick, 1996, undated (Box 14)
    - Nicoletta, Daniel, 2003 (Box 14)
    - Nielson, Al, 1995, undated (Box 14)
    - Nielson, Melanie, 1990-1991, undated (Box 14)
    - Nordeen, Bradford, 2008 (Box 14)
    - Norse, Harold, 1987-1991, undated (Box 14)
    - Northener, Will, 1990 October 29 (Box 14)
    - Notley/Oliver Appeal, 1999 (Box 14)
    - Notley, Alice, 1993-1998, undated (Box 14)
    - Noxzema, Johnny, 1992-1994, undated (Box 14)
    - Nurudin, Azian, 1992 (Box 14)
    - NYFA, 2002 November 07 (Box 14)
    - O'Brian, Geoffrey, 1990-1997, undated (Box 14)
    - O'Leary, Peter, 1996-2007, undated (Box 14)
    - Olin, Jeni, 1989, undated (Box 14)
    - Oliver, Douglas, 1998 October 21 (Box 14)
    - Olson, John, 1996–1997 (Box 14)
    - Olzinski, Eric, 1981 April 05 (Box 14)
    - O'Meara, Biff, 1994 (Box 15)
    - Ondaatje, Michael, 1995-1996, undated (Box 15)
    - O'Neill, Jamie, undated (Box 15)
    - Ortiz, Travis, 1995–1996 (Box 15)
    - Osman, Jena, 1993–1996 (Box 15)
    - Ott, Gil, 1995–1996 (Box 15)
    - Oursler, Tony, undated (Box 15)
    - Owens, Richard, 2012 July 11 (Box 15)
    - Padgett, Ron, undated (Box 15)
    - Palmer, Michael, 1991–1998 (Box 15)
    - Papoulis, Irene, 1981-1983, undated (Box 15)
    - Parkinson, Ariel, undated (Box 15)
    - Pasatieri, Thomas, 1994 November 08 (Box 15)
    - Patterson, Richard North, 1996 (Box 15)
    - Pavlich, Walter, undated (Box 15)
    - Peabody, Richard, 1995, undated (Box 15)
    - Pelton, Ted, 2006 December 21 (Box 15)
    - Penberthy, Jenny, 1995 June 22 (Box 15)
    - Pera, Brian, 2000 (Box 15)
    - Perelman, Bob, 1990-1996, undated; 2 (Box 15)
    - Perloff, Marjorie, 1995 (Box 15)
    - Perrizo, James E., 1991 (Box 15)
    - Persky, Stan, 1985–1991 (Box 15)
    - Peters, Margot, 1985 October 23 (Box 15)
    - Peters, Nancy, 1993–2005 (Box 15)
    - Peters, Robert, 1985-1991, undated (Box 15)
    - Peterson, Ann, 1988–1989 (Box 15)
    - Pettet, Simon, 1993, undated (Box 15)
    - Pettibon, Raymond, 1991-1992, undated; 4 (Box 15)
    - Philip, M. Nourbese, 1996-1997, undated (Box 15)
    - Phillips, Frances, 1987–1995 (Box 15)
    - Phillips, Lisa, 1996 July 09 (Box 15)
    - Picano, Felice, 1987-1992, undated (Box 15)
    - Pierce, Ryan, 2006 May 27 (Box 15)
    - Pimlott, Justine, 2005 December 07 (Box 15)
    - Piston, Job, 2007 November (Box 15)
    - Place, Vanessa, 2014 January 08 (Box 15)
    - Porges, Maria, 1987 (Box 15)
    - Potter, Stephen, 1988-1999, undated (Box 15)
    - Potts, Randall, 1992–1994 (Box 15)
    - Powell, Douglas, 1995, undated (Box 15)
    - Powers, Ann, 1991, undated (Box 15)
    - Pradel, Karl, 1994-1995, undated (Box 15)
    - Pratt, Minnie Bruce, 1989 (Box 15)
    - Pressler, Charlotte, 1994-1996, undated (Box 15)
    - Prevallet, Kristin, 1994-2003, undated (Box 15)
    - Price, Larry, undated (Box 15)
    - Price, Michael, undated (Box 15)
    - Pritchett, Patrick, 1997–1998 (Box 15)
    - Pritikin, Renny, 2005 (Box 15)
    - Private Workshop, 2007 December (Box 15)
    - Purdy, James, 1987-1992, undated (Box 15)
    - Putt, Paula, undated (Box 15)
    - Quart, Alissa, 1998, undated (Box 15)
    - Quartermain, Meredith, 2002–2005 (Box 15)
    - Quartermain, Peter, 1995-2005, undated (Box 15)
    - Quayle, Marilyn, 1992 April 02 (Box 15)
    - Raphael, Lev, 1977-1993, undated; 3 (Box 15)
    - Ratch, Jerry, 1985-1986, undated (Box 15)
    - Ratcliffe, Michael, 1985-1986, undated (Box 15)
    - Ratcliffe, Stephen, 1987-1994, undated (Box 15)
    - Rattray, David, 1992 (Box 16)
    - Raworth, Tom, 1988-2000, undated (Box 16)
    - Ray, Charles, undated (Box 16)
    - Ray, Rex, 1995-2000, undated (Box 16)
    - Raynor, Debbie, 1987 July 08 (Box 16)
    - Raynor, Debbie and Jim, undated (Box 16)
    - Redl, Harry, 1996, undated (Box 16)
    - Reed, Pat, 1985 December 02 (Box 16)
    - Reed, Paul, 1987-1995, undated (Box 16)
    - Reed, Russell, 2005, undated (Box 16)
    - Regan, Matthias, 1999, undated (Box 16)
    - Rehm, Pam, 1994, undated (Box 16)
    - Reichman, Brett, 1997-2008, undated (Box 16)
    - Reigns, Steven, 2006, undated (Box 16)
    - Reiner, Christopher, 1992 (Box 16)
    - Renwick, Vanessa, 1993 (Box 16)
    - Retallack, Joan, 2004–2005 (Box 16)
    - Revell, Donald, undated (Box 16)
    - Ricard, Rene, 1990-2012, undated (Box 16)
    - Riches, Fr. Pierre, 1992 November 10 (Box 16)
    - Rickert, Paul, 1990 October 05 (Box 16)
    - Riker, Ann, 1981-1991, undated (Box 16)
    - Riley, Blake, 2002, undated (Box 16)
    - Rinder, Larry, 1992-1998, undated (Box 16)
    - Roberts, Jim, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Roberts, Lawrence, 1990-1992, undated (Box 16)
    - Roberts, Suzi, 1992, undated (Box 16)
    - Robertson, Lisa, 1989-2008, undated (Box 16)
    - Robinson, Elizabeth, 1991-1995, undated (Box 16)
    - Robinson, Kit, 1989-2003, undated (Box 16)
    - Roche, Thomas, undated (Box 16)
    - Rodefer, Stephen, 1986-1988, undated (Box 16)
    - Rodin, Renee, 1992, undated (Box 16)
    - Rodney, Janet, 1990 October 13 (Box 16)
    - Roeseler, Karl, 1995 June 10 (Box 16)
    - Rollman, Michelle, 1993-2007, undated (Box 16)
    - Rondinone, Ugo, 2012, undated (Box 16)
    - Ronell, Avital, 1995 (Box 16)
    - Ronk, Martha, 1992 (Box 16)
    - Rorem, Ned, 1988–1989 (Box 16)
    - Rosa, Francesca, 1982-1993, undated; 2 (Box 16)
    - Rosenfield, Kim, 1993-2004, undated (Box 16)
    - Rosenthal, Irving, undated (Box 16)
    - Rosenwasser, Rena, 2003 December 26 (Box 16)
    - Rosenzweig, Phyllis, 1990-2004, undated (Box 16)
    - Ross, George, undated (Box 16)
    - Rose, Sheree, undated (Box 16)
    - Ross, Joe, 1993–1994 (Box 16)
    - Ross, TC, undated (Box 16)
    - Rotenberg, Bettina, 1989-1996, undated; 2 (Box 16)